{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Steam Shower Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62649/":{"taskOID":62649,"originalTaskOID":62649,"setID":9333,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7634,"questionDisplayText":"Shower","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Shower","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20475,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace or move existing shower","answerDisplayText":"Replace or move existing shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20476,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install a new shower (No existing shower)","answerDisplayText":"Install a new shower (No existing shower)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7635,"questionDisplayText":"Plumbing fixtures","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Plumbing fixtures","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20477,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to install new plumbing fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to install new plumbing fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20478,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to install new plumbing fixtures","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to install new plumbing fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7636,"questionDisplayText":"Tile","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Tile","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20479,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to install new tile","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to install new tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20480,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to install new tile","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to install new tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500101,"questionDisplayText":"Part of larger remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this project part of a larger remodel?","shortQuestionText":"Part of larger remodel?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7634,"questionDisplayText":"Shower","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Shower","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20475,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace or move existing shower","answerDisplayText":"Replace or move existing shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20476,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install a new shower (No existing shower)","answerDisplayText":"Install a new shower (No existing shower)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20475,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace or move existing shower","answerDisplayText":"Replace or move existing shower","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20476,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install a new shower (No existing shower)","answerDisplayText":"Install a new shower (No existing shower)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7635,"questionDisplayText":"Plumbing fixtures","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Plumbing fixtures","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20477,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to install new plumbing fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to install new plumbing fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20478,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to install new plumbing fixtures","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to install new plumbing fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20477,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to install new plumbing fixtures","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to install new plumbing fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20478,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to install new plumbing fixtures","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to install new plumbing fixtures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7636,"questionDisplayText":"Tile","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Tile","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20479,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to install new tile","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to install new tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20480,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to install new tile","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to install new tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20479,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes - I plan to install new tile","answerDisplayText":"Yes - I plan to install new tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20480,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No - I do not plan to install new tile","answerDisplayText":"No - I do not plan to install new tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500101,"questionDisplayText":"Part of larger remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this project part of a larger remodel?","shortQuestionText":"Part of larger remodel?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/62649/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62649,"taskName":"Steam Shower - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Steam Shower","xmTaskDescriptor":"Steam Shower Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"shower steam shower sauna","textMessagingName":"Stm Shower Install","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes shower pans, tile, fixtures \u0026 doors.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes shower pans, tile, fixtures \u0026 doors.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to install a steam shower. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated steam shower installers in your area.","htmlTitle":"Steam Shower Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Steam Shower Companies","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":60,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Steam Shower Installation","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Steam Shower Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Steam Shower Project","urlName":"Steam-Shower-Install","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Steam Shower Installation Contractors in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"shower, bathroom, steam, sauna","emcCategoryOid":-12058,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9333,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}